Preliminary Guide to the Federation for American Immigration Reform (FAIR) records, 1867-2006 MS2195
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Court cases, 1867 - 1989; 1949-1989; Series 5
  - Jean vs. Nelson, undated; Series 5 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Jean vs. Nelson, 1984; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Jean vs. Nelson, undated; Series 5 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Jean vs. Nelson, undated; Series 5 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Jean vs. Nelson, undated; Series 5 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Jean vs. Nelson amicus curiae, 1984; Series 5 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Jean vs. Nelson brief, 1985 February; Series 5 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Jean vs. Nelson opinion, undated; Series 5 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Jean vs. Nelson supreme court opinion, 1985 June 26; Series 5 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Jet traders inv. corp vs. Tekair, 1981; Series 5 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Johnson vs. McGowan, 1983 November 2; Series 5 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Johnson vs. Transworld airlines inc., 1983 December 6; Series 5 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - Jones vs. Los Angeles community college district, 1983 March 25; Series 5 (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - Jones vs. Unknown agents of fed. elec. com'n., 1979 August 23; Series 5 (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - Japan whaling vs. American cetacean, 1986; Series 5 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Kahlenberg vs. INS, 1985 June 25; Series 5 (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - Kalaw vs. Ferro, 1987 January 13; Series 5 (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - Karcher vs. Daggett, 1983 June 22; Series 5 (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - Katzenbach vs. Morgan, 1966 June 13; Series 5 (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - Kimm vs. Rosenberg, 1960 June 13; Series 5 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Kirkpatric vs. Preisler, 1969 April 7; Series 5 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Kleiboemer vs. District of Columbia, 1983 March 22; Series 5 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Kleindienst vs. Mandel, 1972 June 29; Series 5 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Klier vs. Wainwright, 1971 November 15; Series 5 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Knauff vs. Shaughnessy, 1950 January 16; Series 5 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Kneeland vs. National collegiate athletic asso., 1987 January 7; Series 5 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Knoetze vs. United States, 1979 March 16; Series 5 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Known to the government cases (1/3), undated; Series 5 (Box 140, Folder 9)
  - Known to the government cases (2/3), undated; Series 5 (Box 140, Folder 10)
  - Known to the government cases (3/3), undated; Series 5 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Known to the government, undated; Series 5 (Box 150, Folder 7)
  - Kremer vs. Chemical construction corp., 1982 May 17; Series 5 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - La Abra silver mining co vs. United States, 1899 December 11; Series 5 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Laird vs. Tatum, 1972 June 26; Series 5 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Landon vs. Plasencia, 1982; Series 5 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Lapeyre vs. United States, 1872; Series 5 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Larson vs. Valente, 1982 April 21; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 27)
  - LaRouche vs. Webster, 1983 April 18; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 26)
  - Lassiter vs. Northampton election board, 1959 June 8; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 28)
  - Lau vs. Nichols, 1974 January 21; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 29)
  - Lepiani vs. Dept of labor and industry, 1979 June 7; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 30)
  - Lesbian/Gay freedom day com inc vs. INS, 1982; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 31)
  - Lewis vs. Gross, 1986 July; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 32)
  - Liberty mutual insurance co vs. Pacific indemnity co, 1977 November 25; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 33)
  - Linda R.S. vs. Richard D. and Texas, 1973 March 5; Series 5 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Linsky vs. Heidelberg eastern inc., 1979 May 18; Series 5 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Local 512 warehouse vs. NLRB, 1986 July 22; Series 5 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - LOK vs. INS, 1982 June 1; Series 5 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Lopez vs. Arrowhead ranches, 1975 September 26; Series 5 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Lopez vs. INS, 1985 April 8; Series 5 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Lopez Tijerina vs. Henry, 1969; Series 5 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Los Angeles vs. Van Davis, 1979 March 27; Series 5 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Louisiana vs. NAACP, 1961 May 22; Series 5 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - LSI computer systems inc vs. United States internat'l trade commission, 1987 October 30; Series 5 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Lubey vs. San Francisco, 1979 December 27; Series 5 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - LULAC vs. INS, 1987 July 22; Series 5 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - LULAC vs. Pasadena, brief, 1987 June 12; Series 5 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - LULAC vs. Pasadena, correspondence, 1987; Series 5 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - LULAC vs. Pasadena, court rules and procedures, 1983; Series 5 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - LULAC vs. Pasadena, media, 1987; Series 5 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - LULAC vs. Pasadena, memo and order, 1987 April 18; Series 5 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - LULAC vs. Pasadena, motion, 1987 April; Series 5 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - LULAC vs. Pasadena, motion, 1987 July 20; Series 5 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - LULAC vs. Pasadena, order, 1987 July 31; Series 5 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - LULAC vs. Pasadena, plaintiffs response, 1987 June 30; Series 5 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Lyng vs. Castillo, 1986 June 27; Series 5 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Lyng vs. Northwestern indian cemetary protection asso., 1988 April 19; Series 5 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Machinery corp of America vs. Gullfiber AB, 1985 October 2; Series 5 (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - Magnano vs. Hamilton, 1934 April 2; Series 5 (Box 73, Folder 25)
  - Maneja vs. Waialua agricultural co ltd, 1955 May 23; Series 5 (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Marden vs. EPA, 1984 December 6; Series 5 (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - Marte vs. INS, 1983; Series 5 (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - Marti-Xiques vs. INS, 1983 September 9; Series 5 (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - Marti-Xiques vs. INS, 1984 September 10; Series 5 (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - Mathews vs. Diaz, 1976 June 1; Series 5 (Box 114, Folder 19)
  - Mathews vs. Diaz, 1976 June 1; Series 5 (Box 82, Folder 26)
  - McClune vs. Shamah, 1979 March 8; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 25)
  - McClure vs. Salvation army, 1972; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - McDonnell douglas corp vs. Green, 1973 May 14; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - McKay vs. Heyison, 1980 February 4; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - McLaughlin vs. Florida, 1964 December 7; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Menachaca vs. Palombo, 1988 July 18; Series 5 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Mester vs. INS, 1988 June 30; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - Mester vs. INS, 1989; Series 5 (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - Mester vs. INS, 1989 September 22; Series 5 (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Mester Manufacturing Co vs. US, DOJ, INS, et. al. (1/5), undated; Series 5 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Mester Manufacturing Co vs. US, DOJ, INS, et. al. (2/5), undated; Series 5 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Mester Manufacturing Co vs. US, DOJ, INS, et. al. (3/5), undated; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Mester Manufacturing Co vs. US, DOJ, INS, et. al. (4/5), undated; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Mester Manufacturing Co vs. US, DOJ, INS, et. al. (5/5), undated; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Miller vs. Robertson, 1924 November 17; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Missouri pacific railway co. vs. Kansas, 1919 January 7; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Mitchell vs. United States, 1971 March 18; Series 5 (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - Monmouth medical center vs. Kwok, 1982 March 26; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Montgomery environmental coalition vs. Fri, 1973 October 31; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Moorhead vs. United States, 1985 October 18; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Moragne vs. State marine lines inc., 1970 June 15; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Moreno-Alaniz vs. INS, 1986 January 26; Series 5 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Morton vs. Ruiz, 1973; Series 5 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Mountain states telephone and telegraph co vs. Pueblo of Santa Ana, 1985 June 10; Series 5 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Multi-process international corp vs. Han, 1987 November 13; Series 5 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - NAACP vs. Alabama, 1958 June 30; Series 5 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - NAACP vs. Button, 1963 January 14; Series 5 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - National association for neighborhood schools of Pittsburgh vs. Board of public education, undated; Series 5 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - National association of counties vs. Baker, 1988 March 11; Series 5 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - National black police association vs. Velde, 1980 May 14; Series 5 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - National center for immigrants rights inc vs. INS, 1983 December 16; Series 5 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - National petrolium refiners asso vs. Federal trade commission, 1973 June 27; Series 5 (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - National tour brokers asso vs. Interstate commerce comission, 1982 January 15; Series 5 (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - Natural resources defense council inc vs. United States EPA, 1984 August 28; Series 5 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - NCIR vs. INS, brief for appellants, 1984 February 22; Series 5 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - NCIR vs. INS, motion for partial stay, 1984 January 5; Series 5 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - NCIR vs. INS, notice to dismiss, 1984 February 21; Series 5 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - NCIR vs. INS, opinion, 1986 June 13; Series 5 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - NCIR vs. INS, opinion, 1984 September 28; Series 5 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - NCIR vs. INS, order, 1985 March 7; Series 5 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - NCIR vs. INS, reply to opposition, 1984 January 26; Series 5 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Newport news vs. EEOC, 1983 June 20; Series 5 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Nicacio vs. INS, 1985 August 16; Series 5 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Non-immigration related cases (discrimination) (1/2), 1977-1985; Series 5 (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - Non-immigration related cases (discrimination) (2/2), 1977-1985; Series 5 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Norfolk southern corp vs. Oberly, 1984 September 25; Series 5 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - North American industries inc vs. Feldman, 1983 December 5; Series 5 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - North Carolina state parts authority vs. Dart containerline co ltd., 1979 February 15; Series 5 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Northeast bancorp inc vs. Woolf, 1983 December 16; Series 5 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Novick vs. City of Los Angeles, 1983 December 14; Series 5 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - NWFWA et al vs. Hon. Richard E Lyng, 1987-1989; Series 5 (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - NWFWA et al vs. Hon. Richard E Lyng, 1987-1989; Series 5 (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - NWFWA et al vs. Hon. Richard E Lyng, 1987-1989; Series 5 (Box 87, Folder 19)
  - NWFWA et al vs. Hon. Richard E Lyng, 1987-1989; Series 5 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - NWFWA et al vs. Hon. Richard E Lyng, 1987-1989; Series 5 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - NWFWA et al vs. Hon. Richard E Lyng, 1987-1989; Series 5 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - NWFWA et al vs. Hon. Richard E Lyng, 1987-1989; Series 5 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - NWFWA et al vs. Hon. Richard E Lyng, 1987-1989; Series 5 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - NWFWA et al vs. Hon. Richard E Lyng, 1987-1989; Series 5 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - NWFWA et al vs. Hon. Richard E Lyng, undated; Series 5 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - NWFWA et al vs. Hon. Richard E Lyng, undated; Series 5 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - NWFWA et al vs. Hon. Richard E Lyng, 1987 June 1 - September 4; Series 5 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - NWFWA et al vs. Hon. Richard E Lyng, 1987 September 9 - November 30; Series 5 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - NWFWA et al vs. Hon. Richard E Lyng, 1988 January 4 - June 29; Series 5 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - NWFWA et al vs. Hon. Richard E Lyng, 1988 July 18 - September 6; Series 5 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - NWFWA et al vs. Hon. Richard E Lyng, 1988 August 11 - October 31; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - NWFWA et al vs. Hon. Richard E Lyng, 1988 September 30 - October 26; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - NWFWA et al vs. Hon. Richard E Lyng, 1988 October 31 - November 23; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - NWFWA et al vs. Hon. Richard E Lyng, 1988 December 19 - 1989 June 4; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - NWFWA et al vs. Hon. Richard E Lyng, attachments in support of intervenor, 1988 September 21; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - NWFWA et al vs. Hon. Richard E Lyng, attachments in support of intervenors, undated; Series 5 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - NWFWA et al vs. Hon. Richard E Lyng, attachments in support of intervenors, undated; Series 5 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - NWFWA et al vs. Hon. Richard E Lyng, attachments in support of intervenors, undated; Series 5 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - NWFWA et al vs. Hon. Richard E Lyng, attachments in support of intervenors, undated; Series 5 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - NWFWA et al vs. Hon. Richard E Lyng, attachments in support of intervenors, 1987 November; Series 5 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - NWFWA et al vs. Hon. Richard E Lyng, attachments in support of intervenors, 1987 November; Series 5 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - NWFWA et al vs. Hon. Richard E Lyng, drafts, 1987; Series 5 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - NWFWA vs. Lyng (1/5), 1988; Series 5 (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - NWFWA vs. Lyng (2/5), 1988; Series 5 (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - NWFWA vs. Lyng (3/5), 1988; Series 5 (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - NWFWA vs. Lyng (4/5), 1988; Series 5 (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - NWFWA vs. Lyng (5/5), 1988; Series 5 (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - NWFWA vs. Lyng (1/3), undated; Series 5 (Box 149, Folder 17)
  - NWFWA vs. Lyng (2/3), undated; Series 5 (Box 149, Folder 18)
  - NWFWA vs. Lyng (3/3), undated; Series 5 (Box 149, Folder 19)
  - Office of consumers council Ohio vs. FERC, 1986; Series 5 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Officers for justice vs. Civil service commission of San Diego, 1979 March 30; Series 5 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Olagues vs. Russoniello (1/4), 1986; Series 5 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Olagues vs. Russoniello (2/4), 1986; Series 5 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Olagues vs. Russoniello (3/4), 1986; Series 5 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Olagues vs. Russoniello (4/4), 1986; Series 5 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Olan: petition for naturalization, 1966 August 15; Series 5 (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - Old colony r. co vs. Commissioner of internal revenue, 1932 February 15; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - Oneida vs. State of New York, 1985 August 26; Series 5 (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - Orantes-Hernandez vs. Meese, 1988 April 29; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - Orantes-Hernandez vs. Thornburgh (1/3), undated; Series 5 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Orantez-Hernandez vs. Thornburgh (2/3), undated; Series 5 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Orantez-Hernandez vs. Thornburgh (3/3), undated; Series 5 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Order of railway conductors of America vs. Swan, 1947 January 13; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - Packard motor car co vs. NLR8, 1947; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Patel vs. Quality Inn South, 1988 June 8; Series 5 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Patel vs. Quality Inn South, 1988 September; Series 5 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Patel vs. Sumani, 1987; Series 5 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Patel vs. Sumani, 1987; Series 5 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Patel vs. Sumani, undated; Series 5 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Patel vs. Sumani, 1986-1988; Series 5 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Patel vs. Sumani (1/5), 1986-1988; Series 5 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Patel vs. Sumani (2/5), 1986-1988; Series 5 (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Patel vs. Sumani (3/5), 1986-1988; Series 5 (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Patel vs. Sumani (4/5), 1986-1988; Series 5 (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - Patel vs. Sumani (5/5), 1986-1988; Series 5 (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - Patel vs. Sumani, undated; Series 5 (Box 144, Folder 13)
  - Patel vs. Sumani Corp, undated; Series 5 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Patel vs. Sumani Corp, 1987 May 27; Series 5 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Patel vs. Sumani Corp, undated; Series 5 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Patel vs. Sumani Corp., 1988; Series 1 (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - Patel vs. Sumani, Patel vs. Quality Inn South, undated; Series 5 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Pennhurst state school and hospital vs. Halderman, 1984 January 23; Series 5 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - People vs. Loera, 1984 September; Series 5 (Box 81, Folder 26)
  - Perales vs. Casillas, 1990 June 25; Series 5 (Box 81, Folder 25)
  - Pesikoff vs. Secretary of labor, undated; Series 5 (Box 81, Folder 24)
  - Petermann vs. International brotherhood of teamsters, 1959 September 30; Series 5 (Box 81, Folder 23)
  - Phillips vs. A&C adjusters, 1965 October 7; Series 5 (Box 81, Folder 21)
  - Piedmont heights civic club inc vs. Moreland, 1981; Series 5 (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - Pinilla vs. Board of review dept of labor and industry, 1978 January 4; Series 5 (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - Plyler vs. Doe, 1980; Series 5 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Plyler vs. Doe, 1982 June 15; Series 5 (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - Plyler vs. Doe, 1982; Series 5 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Portillo vs. G.T price products, 1980; Series 5 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Portillo vs. GT Price, related cases, undated; Series 5 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Possible cases, 1980; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Powell vs. McCormack, 1969 June 16; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Producation tool vs. Employment and training admin, 1982 September 20; Series 5 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - PRUCOL: Garcia vs. Brock, 1986 January - May; Series 5 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - PRUCOL: Garcia vs. Brock, 1986 January - May; Series 5 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Pugh vs. See's candies inc, 1981 February 27; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - Quaker action group vs. Morton, 1971 October 21; Series 5 (Box 81, Folder 27)
  - Quality Inn South et. al. vs. Patel, 1988; Series 5 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Quality Inn South vs. Patel, 1988 November 14; Series 5 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Rafeedie vs. INS (1/3), 1988; Series 5 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Rafeedie vs. INS (2/3), 1988; Series 5 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Rafeedie vs. INS (3/3), 1989; Series 5 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Rafeedie vs. INS, 1988 October 11; Series 5 (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Ramirez vs. Sloss, 1980 April 7; Series 5 (Box 81, Folder 28)
  - Ramos vs. Thornburgh, 1989 July 21; Series 5 (Box 81, Folder 29)
  - Reid vs. INS, 1985 February 28; Series 5 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Republican state central committee of Arizona vs. Ripon society, 1972 August 16; Series 5 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Reynolds vs. United States, 1878; Series 5 (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Rice vs. Sioux City: case notes, undated; Series 5 (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Richards vs. United States, 1962 February 26; Series 5 (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Ridge vs. Verity, undated; Series 5 (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - Ridge vs. Verity, undated; Series 5 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Ridge vs. Verity, undated; Series 7 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Ridge vs. Verity, undated; Series 5 (Box 144, Folder 26)
  - Ridge vs. Verity (1/7), 1988-1989; Series 5 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Ridge vs. Verity (2/7), 1988-1989; Series 5 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Ridge vs. Verity (3/7), 1988-1989; Series 5 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Ridge vs. Verity (4/7), 1988-1989; Series 5 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Ridge vs. Verity (5/7), 1988-1989; Series 5 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Ridge vs. Verity (6/7), 1988-1989; Series 5 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Ridge vs. Verity (7/7), 1988-1989; Series 5 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Ridge vs. Verity (1/3), 1988-1989; Series 5 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Ridge vs. Verity (2/3), 1988-1989; Series 5 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Ridge vs. Verity (3/3), 1988-1989; Series 5 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Ridge vs. Verity briefs (1/2), undated; Series 5 (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Ridge vs. Verity briefs (2/2), undated; Series 5 (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Ridge vs. Verity: defendant's motion for judgment, undated; Series 5 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Ridge vs. Verity drafts (1/6), undated; Series 5 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Ridge vs. Verity drafts (2/6), undated; Series 5 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Ridge vs. Verity drafts (3/6), undated; Series 5 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Ridge vs. Verity drafts (4/6), undated; Series 5 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Ridge vs. Verity drafts (5/6), undated; Series 5 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Ridge vs. Verity drafts (6/6), undated; Series 5 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Ridge vs. Verity: exhibitions and declarations, undated; Series 5 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Ridge vs. Verity motion for judgement (1/2), undated; Series 5 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Ridge vs. Verity motion for judgement (2/2), undated; Series 5 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Ridge vs. Verity: Siegel declaration, 1988 December 7; Series 5 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Rios vs. Altamont farms inc., 1985 February 5; Series 5 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - Rios vs. Enterprise Ass'n Steamfitters, 1987; Series 5 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Rite-research vs. Costie, 1981 May 26; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Rivas vs. Donovan, 1986 February 28; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Rivera vs. INS, 1986 June 13; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Roach vs. Dresser industrial value and instrument division, 1980 July 17; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Roberto vs. Hartford fire insurance co., 1949 October 27; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Roberto vs. Hartford fire, 1949 October 27; Series 5 (Box 114, Folder 22)
  - Roe vs. Casey, 1978 December 11; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - Roshan vs. Smith, 1985 August 6; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 31)
  - Rubio vs. Employment division, Oregon, 1984 January 18; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 32)
  - Rulon-Miller vs. International business machines corporation, 1984 November 29; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 33)
  - St. Francis college et. al vs. Ghaidan Al-Khazraji, 1987 May 18; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Sanctuary litigation, 1987; Series 5 (Box 144, Folder 15)
  - Sagebrush rebellion inc. vs. Watt, 1983 August 19; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Sample motions, undated; Series 5 (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - Santa Clara county vs. Southern pacific railroad co., 1886 May 10; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - SAW resource material, 1980-1986; Series 5 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Saxbe vs. Bustos/Cardona vs. Saxbe, 1974 November 25; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Schlesinger vs. Reservists, 1974 June 25; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Seamans vs. Standard oil, 1984 August 30; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of state of Maryland vs. Munson, 1984 June 26; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Shapiro vs. Thompson, 1969 April 21; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Shapiro vs. Wells fargo realty, 1984; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Sherbert vs. Verner, 1963 June 17; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Sida vs. INS, 1985 July 2; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Sierra club vs. Dept. of the interior, 1972 April 19; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Sierra club vs. Morton, 1972 April 19; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Silva vs. Bell, 1979 October 18; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Simon vs. Eastern Kentucky welfare rights organization, 1976 June 1; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Simonson vs. International bank of washington, 1963 January 4; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - Sioux valley vs. Butz, 1973 November 29; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - Sleddens vs. Shaughnessy, 1949 October 27; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 23)
  - Smith vs. INS, 1988 April 11; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 24)
  - Smith vs. Meese, 1987 June 30; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Smith vs. Robinson, 1984 July 5; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 26)
  - Smith vs. U.S. Navy, 1983 October 11; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 27)
  - Smith vs. Wade, 1983 April 20; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 28)
  - Snapp and son vs. Puerto Rico, 1982 July 1; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 29)
  - Soberal-Perez vs. Heckler, 1983 August 30; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 30)
  - Solis-Ramirez vs. INS, 1985 April 25; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 31)
  - Soloranzo vs. Secretary of health and human services, 1983 January 28; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 32)
  - Spangler vs. Pasadena, 1977 April 27; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 33)
  - Spiess vs. C. Iton and co., 1981 April 24; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 34)
  - Standard oil co. of New Jersey vs. United States, 1910 October; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 35)
  - Steele vs. National firearms act branch, 1985 March 22; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 37)
  - Strauss vs. A.L. Randall co., inc., 1983 July 6; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 38)
  - Sudomir vs. McMahon, 1985 August 12; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 39)
  - Sumitomo shoji america, inc vs. Avagliano, 1982 June 15; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 3)